{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 60 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice, we get a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 24 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars, we get a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate and 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 36 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 26 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. The price of a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place is the same as that of a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 26 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate, we get a scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "7", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. Combine with the fact that a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate, we get a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ. 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. A Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 8 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 8 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost a dollar less than a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice. 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 69 dollars. A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 4 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 69 dollars, we get a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. A burger at Urban Plate costs 22 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars more than a creme brulee at Urban Plate. 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate and 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 60 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "14", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate and 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 60 dollars, we get a creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 41 dollars. A Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 37 dollars more than a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine. A Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 37 dollars more than a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine. A pizza at Urban Plate costs 34 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ and 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 46 dollars. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 17 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that a Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, we get a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A burger at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost 50 dollars. 2 burgers at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 58 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 burgers at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 58 dollars, we get a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 37 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 24 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 17 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a lasagna at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 24 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place, we get a lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "A pie at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars. A pie at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than a fruit tart at Texas BBQ. A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pie at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than a fruit tart at Texas BBQ, we get a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Bistro Nice and a burger at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 2 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 2 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice, we get a burger at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. The price of 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. The price of a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 16 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that the price of a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, we get a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ. A Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. A pizza at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, we get a Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "A burger at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. 3 pies at Mike's Place and 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 69 dollars. A pie at Mike's Place costs 3 dollars more than a pie at Bistro Nice. A pie at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pie at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that a pie at Mike's Place costs 3 dollars more than a pie at Bistro Nice, we get a pie at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 41 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Urban Plate. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Urban Plate, we get a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and a fruit tart at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and a fruit tart at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars, we get a fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. A pie at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 66 dollars. A pie at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a pie at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "8", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 66 dollars, we get a pie at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 33 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. 3 burgers at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 66 dollars. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 56 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "7", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place, we get a Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 35 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. A Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs a dollar less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 35 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice, we get a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. The price of 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars. A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "10", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. Combine with the fact that the price of 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate and 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 48 dollars. A Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate and 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 60 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate and 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 48 dollars, we get a Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place. A pizza at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars. 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 9 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pizza at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars. Combine with the fact that a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place, we get a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than a pie at Bistro Nice. 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a pie at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "10", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place, we get a pie at Mike's Place costs 10 dollars."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice. A pie at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "8", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice, we get a pie at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 27 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 13 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 27 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ, we get a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars more than a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 37 dollars more than a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 58 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "14", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 58 dollars, we get a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "9", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate, we get a scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars. A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, we get a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars more than 2 pies at Texas BBQ. A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars more than a pie at Bistro Nice. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "14", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pie at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that a creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars more than 2 pies at Texas BBQ, we get a creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. A burger at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. A burger at Urban Plate costs 19 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place. 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a pizza at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place, we get a pizza at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Mike's Place. 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 5 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 5 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice, we get a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 22 dollars. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, we get a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 13 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. A burger at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 29 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 13 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place, we get a burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice and a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 4 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place, we get a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 27 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 19 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "9", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 19 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, we get a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice. A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice, we get a scrambled egg at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 8 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 45 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 45 dollars, we get a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. A Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 60 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 60 dollars, we get a Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. A pie at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars less than a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a pie at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that a pie at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars less than a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, we get a pie at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 pies at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars more than a pie at Taste Good Cuisine. The price of a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of a pie at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 7 dollars more than a pie at Mike's Place. A pie at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pie at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars more than a pie at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "The price of 2 burgers at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 2 burgers at Mike's Place. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost 27 dollars. A burger at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a fruit tart at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that the price of 2 burgers at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 2 burgers at Mike's Place, we get a burger at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 37 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars less than a lasagna at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars less than a lasagna at Mike's Place, we get a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. A lasagna at Texas BBQ and a lasagna at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 8 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a lasagna at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that a lasagna at Texas BBQ and a lasagna at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars, we get a lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost 41 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "10", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 5 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars more than 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "7", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars more than 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Mike's Place. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ cost 41 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Mike's Place, we get a Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 18 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice, we get a pizza at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 27 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 54 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 27 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate, we get a Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice. A pie at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars more than a pie at Taste Good Cuisine. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 25 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pie at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. Combine with the fact that a pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars less than a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, we get a pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 11 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 47 dollars. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "7", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 47 dollars, we get a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Texas BBQ and a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 14 dollars. A fruit tart at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. Combine with the fact that a fruit tart at Texas BBQ and a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 14 dollars, we get a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs a dollar less than 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice. A pizza at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "9", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, we get a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars."}
{"problem": "A pie at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. A pie at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. A pie at Bistro Nice and a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pie at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that a pie at Bistro Nice and a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars, we get a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 10 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that a Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, we get a Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars more than 2 burgers at Bistro Nice. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars less than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars more than 2 burgers at Bistro Nice, we get a burger at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars less than a creme brulee at Urban Plate. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than a creme brulee at Bistro Nice. 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 50 dollars. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice and 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 50 dollars, we get a creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. A Cobb salad at Urban Plate and a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 23 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. A Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that a Cobb salad at Urban Plate and a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars, we get a Greek salad at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A burger at Bistro Nice costs 3 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than a burger at Bistro Nice. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. A burger at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that a burger at Bistro Nice costs 3 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice, we get a lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 29 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place. 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place and 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 24 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "10", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 29 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place, we get a Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 10 dollars."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. A burger at Mike's Place costs 16 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "7", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place, we get a scrambled egg at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 34 dollars. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 34 dollars, we get a burger at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A pie at Urban Plate and 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 36 dollars. 2 pies at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 52 dollars. A pie at Urban Plate and 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 30 dollars. A pie at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pie at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that a pie at Urban Plate and 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 30 dollars, we get a pie at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars less than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ. 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars more than a fruit tart at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. Combine with the fact that a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars less than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, we get a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 31 dollars. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "10", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice, we get a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 24 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "9", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place, we get a Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars."}
{"problem": "3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 18 dollars more than 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars more than a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 29 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "8", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 18 dollars more than 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 8 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 44 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 32 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "7", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. Combine with the fact that a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 32 dollars, we get a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 4 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars. A Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 32 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 32 dollars, we get a Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 17 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate and a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 50 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate and 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 17 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice, we get a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A burger at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 26 dollars less than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice. A Greek salad at Bistro Nice costs 3 dollars less than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice, we get a Greek salad at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ and a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "9", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ and a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars, we get a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate, we get a creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a lasagna at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ, we get a lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Urban Plate. 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 31 dollars more than a creme brulee at Bistro Nice. 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 20 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 20 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice, we get a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 4 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "9", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars, we get a Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Texas BBQ and a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. A pizza at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 4 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a pizza at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that a pizza at Texas BBQ and a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ cost 26 dollars, we get a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 22 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 33 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "9", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 33 dollars, we get a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 35 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 35 dollars, we get a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 4 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 2 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place. A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "10", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 2 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, we get a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 20 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. A scrambled egg at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 29 dollars. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "5", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. Combine with the fact that a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 29 dollars, we get a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 17 dollars less than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ and 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 87 dollars. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ and a burger at Bistro Nice cost 35 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 17 dollars less than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ, we get a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a fruit tart at Bistro Nice. 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 63 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars less than a fruit tart at Bistro Nice. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. Combine with the fact that a fruit tart at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a fruit tart at Bistro Nice, we get a fruit tart at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars."}
{"problem": "A burger at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. 3 burgers at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 22 dollars. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine and a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost 11 dollars. 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 45 dollars. A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs a dollar more than a fruit tart at Mike's Place. 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 55 dollars. A fruit tart at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "11", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a fruit tart at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 55 dollars, we get a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 18 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ, we get a lasagna at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 2 dollars more than a pie at Urban Plate. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 5 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 5 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars, we get a burger at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "15", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, we get a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "9", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. Combine with the fact that a creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, we get a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars."}
{"problem": "A burger at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. 3 burgers at Urban Plate and 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 51 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice, we get a burger at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 51 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "6", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, we get a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 16 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "8", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. Combine with the fact that a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 16 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ, we get a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 17 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 44 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. Combine with the fact that a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 44 dollars, we get a lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 63 dollars. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 10 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 8 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "13", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 8 dollars. Combine with the fact that 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 10 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice, we get a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 27 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 39 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "12", "proof": "It is given as a fact that a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. Combine with the fact that 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 27 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, we get a burger at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars."}
